["Boss" playing]
♪ Imma boss
Tell 'em not today ♪
♪ Swervin' on these chickens
Cluck out my lane ♪
♪ Imma boss
Outta my way ♪
♪ Or just do every little thing
That I say ♪
♪ I'm the frickin' greatest
I'm the raise they exclaimated ♪
♪ LA Times
I stay on page six… ♪
Guess what? I got another
email from a guy from France,
"Hey, I want to do into real estate."
I'm, like, "Oh God."
[Davina] Who has time to waste like that?
Who does more work in the office,
Brett or Niko?
-[Mary] It's a tie.
-[Jason] It's a total tie.
-[Davina] Who's more in the office?
-Yeah, Niko does show up more.
He's got a much better attendance record.
[Mary] Oh, he definitely has
a better attendance record.
I'm so excited. I've been planning
and seeing designs and renderings
for so long on this wedding,
and now it's finally coming together.
[Maya] Are you nervous?
I'm not nervous at all.
I'm, like, the best planner ever.
I'm so detail-oriented,
I live for this stuff.
But there's tons of surprises
for the wedding.
It's more theatrical, it's very dramatic.
I mean, you know me.
I just don't wanna tell you the details--
I don't wanna ask any more questions.
[Maya] I wanna be surprised.
So how many peoples you have?
So it's gonna be really small.
It's just close family and friends.
We have, like, under 80.
-Wow. That's a good amount.
-[Christine] Yeah.
-[Maya] And everybody all going?
-Yeah, everyone's coming, yeah.
How about Chrishell?
Um, I sent her a message
after all this went down.
I was like, "Hope you're doing well.
Hey, I'm so sorry. I'm just checking in.
Are you coming to the wedding?
You know, I totally understand
your decision either way.
But do you want chicken, beef or fish?"
-Probably a hard situation.
-[Maya] It's hard because you're going
through something that someone is doing
exactly the opposite.
-Yeah.
-[Maya] It sucks.
[soulful pop playing]
♪ Hey girl, you better watch out
No one's gonna push me around ♪
Hey, beautiful!
Hi, guys!
[Christine] How are you?
-[Maya] Welcome back.
-Well, you look snazzy.
Thank you very much.
You're back.
-[groans] Good to see you.
-You too.
How was your trip with your family?
It was really good,
and it feels like
I could breathe a little bit and…
I wanted to come back
and make sure nobody took my desk.
[all laugh]
[Maya] Amanza was eyeing on it, but no.
-[loud bang]
-Oops.
[Christine] Oh my God,
was that your laptop?
I've got it all together, guys.
-[Davina] Is it okay?
-It's fine. Everything's gonna be fine.
-[Maya] It's only a laptop.
-[Davina] Yeah.
Going home and being with my family
gave me the courage
that I needed to kind of face everybody
and step back into the office
and move forward.
Did I miss anything?
[Christine] We're talking
about wedding planning and stuff.
I'm going to the dress shop
to go do a second fitting, so…
right now it's just the shell.
Oh my God.
Your wedding is in a few days.
I forgot about…
I know, it's on Sunday.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't even, like, RSVP or anything.
[Christine] No, I totally understand,
you were preoccupied.
You do not have to apologize
or explain anything.
I got fish for you.
I'm wearing black
and all my guests are wearing white.
I could wear my wedding dress.
Oh.
For Halloween I can be
a dead bride and just put blood--
You put blood and then burn it after.
That's the fucking spirit, Chrishell.
I like that.
["Take the Crown" playing]
♪ Forget what they say
What they say ♪
♪ 'Cause one of these days
We're gonna take the crown ♪
[fades into hip hop beat]
♪ Ooh wow wow
Ooh wow wow ♪
♪ Show ya how I do this thang
Show ya how I do this thang ♪
♪ Let me, let me ♪
♪ Show ya how I do this thang
Show ya how I do this thang ♪
♪ Let me, let me… ♪
-[Davina] Christine!
-[gasps] Hi, guys!
-[Davina] Oh, sorry.
-How are you?
-[Heather] Good. Are you ready?
-I don't know, we'll see.
I have so much stuff
I've been dealing with.
I have, you know, like,
flowers coming in from vendors.
All this stuff, it's just insane.
-The house is packed.
-So what's all this for?
-We're having a family dinner before.
-[Heather] They're so beautiful.
They brought all these flowers in,
and then they left them down here
and it's the only spot in the house
that we can sit.
-Hope you don't mind.
-[Heather] It's awesome.
Everything looks like--
To be in the nitty-gritty
of the planning.
[Christine sighs] There's so much stuff
going on.
-How's this all gonna get done?
-[Davina] How's the fitting going?
-Yeah, how's the dress?
-It's not fitting right or--
I went to go try the dress on,
and, like, it didn't fit.
Like, my body's changed,
like, my boobs are fucking huge,
and they're having to, like,
-alter and change everything.
-Oh no!
But has that ever happened?
I mean, no.
My body's, like, always been the same.
It's always the same.
-But my boobs are huge.
-That's why it's weird.
They look gigantic.
Are you pregnant?
No, I'm not.
Is there milk in there?
I'm not pregnant. There's no way.
Weren't you sick? You were throwing up.
I've been so sick lately.
I was… I was, like, throwing up.
I just don't feel good.
And certain foods, I'm just, like--
You're throwing up, your boobs are huge,
-you feel nauseous.
-She's in denial.
[Heather] I think Christine is not ready
to be a mom.
It's a lot of work, and I think
she would need probably ten nannies.
[laughs]
But her boobs are gonna look really good
in that dress.
I think she can keep her belly down
for a while, though, and not show.
So I think we're good.
Okay, enough about all this shenanigans,
I wanna get some tea.
What's going on?
-Um, hashtag awkward.
-[laughs]
-Um, I know you had an interview with Us.
-Oh yeah, Tarek and I had an interview
for Us Weekly about us moving in together.
We're talking about houses
and living together and love
and kids, blah blah blah, then,
"And how are you supporting Chrishell?"
That's so messed up
that they just throw that in there.
It was just super fast,
and I was just, like,
"Oh, um… yeah, you know, uh…
I haven't gotten to talk to her.
Just a little texting…
but I'm being supportive
and giving her her space--
-Right.
-…She's a strong woman."
It caught me off guard
when they said that.
But that's what they do.
If they'd emailed me and said,
"Can you comment on this?"
I'd have said, "No."
What was the headline of the article?
[Davina] It was
"Heather Rae talks about Chrishell."
-[gasps] Wait.
-So they took what I said about Chrishell
and they used that as a story.
I texted Chrishell right away
and was like,
"Hey this was completely, like,
I completely got caught off guard."
We were doing an interview
about Tarek and I--
-[Davina] They know it.
-…and they snuck it in.
No, I think they know
that you didn't have any bad intentions.
We all know that, you know?
Well, I hope they know that.
I messaged Chrishell telling her, so…
She knows that.
She sees your "Baking Cookies" articles,
she see your "Going to CVS" articles…
[laughs]
…she sees
"You Going to the Restaurant" articles.
"I'm Going to Sleep."
[Christine] She sees you
being compared to other girls.
She sees all the articles.
[laughs]
[stifling laugh]
Unless you're Jennifer Aniston,
paparazzi doesn't just follow you around.
I mean, exposure doesn't come cheap.
You know? [snickers]
I would like to clear something up.
There are things that are set up,
but I don't call paparazzi to show up--
-But maybe he is though. Not you.
-No, he's not.
-He would tell me if he was.
-[Davina] Okay.
People hire publicists and whole teams
to get their name out there.
They'll call or drop hints.
That's pretty much
how the paparazzi thing works.
It's not, like, in the bushes,
like, Amanza-style.
People see where we are on Instagram.
People show up. Like, us living together--
-[Davina] But the cookies--
-[Christine] The cookies!
-[Davina] I don't know.
-[Heather] It's on fucking Instagram.
You have someone
on retainer monthly to do these things.
No, that's bullshit!
She helps with the Us Weekly things.
I can't help that people are interested
in Tarek and my life.
You guys, if you guys, like--
I'm pissed off. You're fucking annoying me
'cause you keep saying it
-and pissing me off.
-[Davina] Why are you mad?
You guys are making fun of me.
It's fuckin' annoying.
You've done this four fucking times.
You have! It's annoying. I'm over it.
-Seriously.
-Heather, we're just being funny.
[Heather] It's not fucking funny
trying to make me look stupid.
-[Davina] We're not.
-We're not.
[Heather] You have nothing nice to say.
Stop being fucking rude!
We have nothing nice to say? Oh my God.
[dramatic music fades out]
[hip-hop music playing]
♪ Cherry top, lookin' kinda glossy ♪
♪ Keep it hot
You all the way picante ♪
♪ Imma boss
I work, work when I want ♪
♪ Self-made
No matter what the cost ♪
♪ I go pick a grande
Like my mama taught me ♪
♪ Don't care what your friends say
I can do this all day ♪
♪ I go, I go pick a grande
Like my mama taught me ♪
♪ Don't care what your friends say
I, I can do this all day… ♪
Chrishell is not the only one
who's getting listings in the Valley.
I'm excited to show Jason
this beautiful property.
-[Jason] Maya?
-Hey.
-Hey. How are you?
-You made it.
Honestly, after last night,
I thought, like…
It's not even fair that you can't drink.
I remember those days
when I stayed up past 11 p.m.
-You don't have the remorse that I have.
-Ay, ay, ay.
I wanna show you a little bit.
Yeah, so you see open floor plan,
brand new construction.
It's a good option for someone
who maybe cannot afford the Hills
but wants the cool space
and still be close to the Hill.
I think that's a great location.
What's normally ugly, a retaining wall,
he did a decent job kinda masking that.
-[Maya] Yeah.
-Kind of artistic.
Let me guess, this is probably worth,
two-three, two-four,
and he probably wants two-eight.
You nailed it.
Even hangover you got this.
Um, even if we start--
I know we're starting a little bit high,
we can test it for the first three weeks,
see how it does.
[Jason] It's a cool property.
I knew you were gonna like it.
It's sexy--
It gets us out in the Valley again,
which is great.
-Exactly and plus--
-Fully solidifies us.
-Show me the rest.
-[Maya] Yeah.
Loft-style.
[Jason] This is nice.
-How many square feet is the house?
-It's a little bit north of the 3,000.
So you have a huge walk-in closet.
-[Jason] Yeah, nice bathroom too.
-[Maya] Nice bathroom, dual sink.
And here's your master bedroom.
It's open to the outdoor.
[Jason] This is cool. I like this,
this vantage right here.
Yeah. I'm excited to take this listing.
Obviously, I think it's probably gonna be
the last listing I'm gonna have in L.A.,
until obviously, I have to go back
to Miami. Give birth.
That's the reason I'm here.
I wanna talk about your plans.
My goal is to get my broker's license
before I have the second baby in Florida.
I've been thinking a lot about my future,
obviously, with another baby on the way,
and I just want to see if you would be
considering opening an office in Miami.
I think there's a market
for the Oppenheim Group in Miami.
The houses are obviously luxury, sexy,
it's a lot of money there.
That's what ideally I would like to do.
I have to be realistic at some point,
I can't just be everywhere.
You're someone that I trust and that I…
you know, value.
And I don't wanna lose you.
And I think you do a great job.
But, it's a significant financial
investment, and it's risky.
And Miami isn't my first choice,
to be honest.
I'd probably choose New York over Miami.
Or Orange County.
There's also more confluence
with my clients between New York and L.A.
You know,
seeing what happened with Chrishell
opened my eyes a little bit more
that I should actually put my marriage
and family as a priority.
But opening an office,
it's not that easy and it's not cheap.
So we'll see.
Listen, I mean, we can still talk.
But I can't commit to anything right now.
Yeah, I have a lot to think about.
I don't know what I'm going to do,
if L.A. even fits me.
Obviously, I'm going to keep my license
with the O Group and just see.
See what happens.
Yeah.
["These Streets" playing]
♪ These streets
They're mean ♪
♪ You gotta fight if you want to eat ♪
♪ They're gonna try to take you
Never let 'em break you… ♪
I am so excited to show you this property.
I know you came from Calabasas,
-but just give me a chance.
-[Karamo] I will.
You work a lot down here,
so this home would be perfect for you.
Listen, you know I trust you, so…
whatever you think is best,
I'll go for it.
Good, good.
Karamo from Queer Eye
is one of my friends and clients.
He's looking to relocate.
I think he's looking for a pool,
a great place to cook and a view.
What more would you want?
♪ It gets me every time I see it ♪
♪ And I'm okay
Nice to meet ya… ♪
-[Karamo] This is beautiful, wow.
-Isn't it? So this is a four bedroom,
three bathroom.
It's just over 2,500 square feet--
-This is nice.
-…at two-nine.
[Karamo] The light
that just comes in naturally is beautiful.
[Christine] I know.
This is an architecturally
significant property
because it was built by Richard Neutra,
who specialized in
all these great lines that he did,
the flat roofs, the wooden beams,
the metal, the white.
This stove, how cute is this?
It's Tiffany Blue.
[Karamo] This is adorable!
-I love this wood. It's so nice.
-Great mid-century vibe. Yeah.
-I started a skin-care business--
-Of course.
-…so I want somewhere--
-I saw!
Thank you. So I want somewhere
that I can have an office space
for the business to grow
but also have the house space.
-I'll give you free stuff.
-I would love that.
-I'll hook you up.
-Thank you.
Gosh, I've been so--
Someone's been stressed.
I haven't been. My wedding planner's
been stressed planning. It should be--
-Oh, for the-- Yes! Oh my gosh!
-I know.
-Your wedding is going to be epic.
-So exciting!
You're gonna have a Ferris wheel!
-Yours is gonna be over-the-top.
-I can't wait.
-It makes sense us going
-over-the-top everything.
-Right? So extra.
So this is a great guest bedroom.
-Yeah. It's beautiful.
-Really big. Nice view of the patio.
-Gorgeous.
-And this would be a really great office.
And then
I'll show you the master downstairs,
-it's really gorgeous.
-This would be a really good office space.
["Gimme Some More" playing]
♪ Gimme some more of what you got… ♪
I love the bedroom.
The lighting's great.
The bedroom is beautiful,
I only have one issue, is that I'm 6'3",
and these beams are really low.
-I'm seeing that now.
-And so,
it's kind of hard.
And then Ian and I
like to have, like, wild sex.
So, like, we would be doing,
like, some craziness,
and it's, like,
I don't wanna, like, hit his head,
like, every time he's up there.
I've had some crazy sex in my day,
but I have never bonked my head
on a ceiling and gotten a concussion.
I don't know
what kind of crazy sex they're into,
but sign me up. Please.
There's one more thing
I do wanna show you, and it's the pool.
-It's really, really gorgeous.
-Okay.
I know you love your pool parties…
-I do love my pool parties.
-…and entertaining. [laughs]
-What do you think?
-[Karamo] Yeah. This is beautiful.
-I love this.
-Yeah.
I mean, I have a pool, as you know, and--
but it's rectangular.
-But I like this sort of circular--
-Yeah.
…grotto vibe, like, you know,
-Playboy Mansion type of vibe.
-It is! I love it!
Karamo's a sweetheart on TV,
but boy, he likes to have fun,
and I like seeing this side of him.
How's work and everything else?
I mean, it's going good, but these bitches
are exhausting me at work.
I mean, the thing is, like,
I work in a group environment
where I'm always with four other people.
-Tell me about it.
-So I understand.
It becomes, like, your second family
and they're always involved in your life.
It's like… we love each other,
but then you have disagreements.
And we're so split apart,
it's, like, you know--
-The girls are?
-The girls are so split apart.
I mean, there's seven of us and,
you know, it's uh…
Mary, Amanza and Chrishell on one side,
and me, Maya,
Heather and Davina on the other.
So it's just like--
-I wanna hang out with that side.
-[Christine] I know. [laughs]
-'Cause we're the fun bad girls.
-I know what that's like.
♪ Oh yeah oh yeah ♪
♪ I love love love love it ♪
♪ Oh yeah oh yeah… ♪
Do you think Jason would be proud of us
working so hard right now?
I know, right? He's at lunch,
and you and I are hustling.
Um, so I just wanted to kinda ask you.
How are you feeling
after the little talk at Christine's?
I felt really bad when I saw you
get upset. I didn't wanna upset you.
It's not like we're sitting there
calling paparazzi to come and follow us.
You have to remember,
Tarek's been on TV
since, like, 2011.
-[Davina] Yeah.
-And he had a very public divorce.
-Yeah, that sucks.
-People are interested in what he's doing.
-Yeah.
-And I'm…
new in his life, so…
they're gonna wanna see
what are we doing? What's going on?
I get defensive and upset about it
because you know how much I love him.
I don't like to make fun of my friends,
you know?
Maybe you hadn't said it before as much,
but Christine, there had been
three other times that she said something.
And for a second I'm like,
is it, like, a jealousy thing?
-I don't know what it is.
-I don't think so.
Maybe she doesn't understand.
I just think that Christine
doesn't really realize how it works,
and she thinks that
everyone calls paparazzi to get attention.
I don't know if she can't handle
that I'm getting more attention than her,
and she needs to be in the spotlight,
but Christine, your day will come.
I just wanna apologize again.
I didn't intend to hurt your feelings.
I know Christine didn't either.
Thank you for apologizing,
I appreciate it.
I mean I got upset, but--
-I don't get upset often…
-[Davina] I don't wanna upset you.
You're gonna come to the wedding, right?
Yeah. Of course.
-Yeah, okay.
-[Heather] I love love. So any chance
I can go to a wedding, I'm gonna go.
-I'm excited. I can't wait.
-[Davina] Me too.
[upbeat pop playing]
♪ There has been too much time
Pretending ♪
♪ It comes so easy
Comes so easy ♪
♪ Now I can face it
Now I can face it… ♪
[Chrishell] Alright,
let's see what you think.
This looks so cute.
It's, like, nice and airy.
-Look at these windows.
-Look at that.
[Mary] I love it.
-Those are some views.
-[Chrishell] Those are some views.
One of the best parts is you're gonna
start getting to know the Hills
so much better.
You've been working around here a lot,
but you're gonna meet all these people
and start getting the listings
when they're ready.
-So schmoozing the neighbors.
-[repeats] That's true.
-Yeah.
-[Chrishell] Could be a leg up on, uh…
-getting back into work, so…
-Yeah.
This is like-- this has good vibes.
-[Chrishell] I like that.
-Really good vibes.
-[Chrishell] Um, check out the kitchen?
-[Mary] Yeah.
Oh, this is cute!
You have views from your kitchen
for when you don't cook.
When I eat my Postmates that's a--
at the countertop.
And I can…
Like, it just feels good,
it's a perfect size, furnished.
Like, it checks all the boxes.
-Perfect area. It's like--
-She loves it.
-I know! She's loving it.
-[dog squeaks]
[Chrishell] I heard
you and Brett sold Alpine.
[Mary] Yup,
it went really quickly for 8.6.
[Chrishell] Congrats! You are killing it!
I didn't end up selling it to Oliver,
but we did sell it to a family
that was just looking
for more of a family-style home.
[Chrishell] Oh my God, that's amazing.
-I'm so proud of you.
-Yeah.
Have you given any more thought
to Christine's wedding? Are you gonna go?
-Um, I wanna go.
-[Mary] Yeah.
[Chrishell] It's hard
because I don't know what's planned,
and I don't know
how sentimental it's gonna be.
And I'm just doing as best I can to like--
Yeah.
…compartmentalize and today, like, okay.
Like, can't cry today, like,
today is like, business,
stay productive, like…
-Yeah.
-…stay focused.
But if I'm watching two people
say their vows, and I'm thinking about…
-It's torture.
-[Chrishell] It'd be impossible not to.
So… I haven't decided
just because I don't really know yet
if it's a good environment for me
to run into right now.
Have you talked to Justin?
[scoffs] I have not.
-That sucks.
-[Chrishell] I know.
[Mary] He needs to have a conversation
with you.
Like, to explain what's going on
and that he wants…
a divorce. Not… a freaking text.
Who does that?
-Well, I can think of one person.
-I can think of one person!
Yeah.
Oh my… [stifled]
Want me to rough him up a little bit?
Oh my gosh. No, I just--
I need my friends to be around me
and be wonderful as they are.
And I probably am gonna need
some wine or vodka.
I know where a liquor store is.
-This is gonna be good.
-Yeah.
I feel good energy at this place.
If you have to start over,
I think this is a great place to do it.
I've started over
in some real shitty scenarios.
-[Mary] Me too.
-This…
Yeah, you're gonna do just fine.
[upbeat pop playing]
[fades into "All Eyes On This"]
♪ All eyes, all eyes, all eyes on this ♪
♪ Better get ready
This is where it’s going down ♪
♪ Look here got everybody talking now ♪
♪ Imma buzzin'
Imma buzzin' ♪
♪ I got the buzz
Got all eyes watching this ♪
♪ Watch this
Be prepared to be amazed ♪
♪ Prepare to be amazed ♪
♪ All eyes on this… ♪
[Heather] Oh my God.
-[Davina] I love this!
-[Maya] Wow.
♪ All eyes on this ♪
♪ Don’t look away
Got something you ain't seen before ♪
♪ There’s no escape
Got a thing that you can’t ignore ♪
[Jason] Let's get this party started.
♪ Prepare to be amazed
Prepare to be amazed ♪
♪ All eyes on this ♪
♪ All eyes ♪
♪ All eyes on… ♪
-[Romain] Holy shit.
-Swans.
What the fuck? I thought they were fake.
And then…
Wow.
[Jason] This is incredible. Look at this.
Look at these swans,
they're just chilling out, bro.
-[Maya] This awesome.
-We're over here.
[Davina] Okay.
[Heather] Does anyone know
if Chrishell's coming?
[Maya] She is?
[Mary] I don't know.
♪ Better get moving
you know this ain't gonna last ♪
♪ Better get it
'Cause you know this is going fast ♪
♪ All eyes on this… ♪
Wow!
Oh my God.
-[Maya] Oh, wow. She made it.
-[Chrishell] Hey.
[Mary] You came!
[Chrishell] Oh my gosh. How are you, guys?
[Maya] Wow, you made it.
[Chrishell] You guys all look so gorgeous.
[Brett] That's how I wake up.
I have four female violinists
in my bedroom.
[Maya] Must be nice, Brett.
[Jason] You know what?
I feel like I'm in a Chanel fashion show.
[Brett] Yeah, that's exactly it.
Can't be in everything, Romain.
Get your fat head out. It's the girls.
[Mary] I can't believe
she's getting married.
[Heather] Can you guys believe
she's getting married?
[Brett] Kind of.
-[Maya] Believe it when I see it.
-[Brett] When they say yes.
-[Jason] When Christian says yes.
-He can still say no.
Dude, those swans are so well-behaved.
They're not trying to go anywhere.
Oh my God. There's a swan.
There's swans up there.
Oh my God.
[Jason] They're drugged up right now.
[Heather] Don't say that!
Those swans are rolling their asses off.
-[Heather] No!
-[Jason] No idea where they are.
-[Maya] They'll cook them for dinner.
-[Heather] Oh my God.
What'd you order for--
Did you get the fish or the swan?
-[all laugh]
-[Heather] You guys!
Imagine? I'd-- I'd throw up.
[Chrishell] Well, I made it.
I wanted to be here for my friends.
And even though Christine and I
have definitely had our ups and downs,
this is a huge day for her. You only--
Well, I was gonna say
you only get married once.
Fuck, that's depressing.
I thought it was supposed to start
at 5:30.
-[Mary] What time is it?
-[Amanza] 7:00.
[Mary] It was supposed to start at 5:00.
Two hours--
Amanza, she might have broken your record.
[Amanza] I was an hour and 45 minutes late
walking down the aisle.
And I was having a panic.
God was like, "Don't do this,
'cause it's only gonna last two years!
Just don't do it!"
But I didn't listen.
-You okay?
-[Chrishell] Okay.
["I Am The Diamond" playing]
♪ Tell me somethin’ I don't know ♪
♪ Take me somewhere I won't go ♪
♪ Baby do it tonight ♪
Is she coming?
[Maya] She's so cute.
[Heather] She's coming! She's coming!
She's coming. Yay!
♪ It might be wrong but I'm not right ♪
[Brett] No way, what the fuck is that?
What is that?
[Maya] What is that?
[Mary] What's happening right now?
I'm almost scared.
Snow. There's snow coming.
Oh my God, it is snow.
[Heather] It's snowing!
That is so dope.
Look at this, this is so dope.
[Amanza] Oh, it's actually cold.
[Romain] That's insane.
[Davina] Oh my God.
[all oohing and ahhing]
[Heather]  Oh my gosh.
Oh, wow. Wow. Is this for real?
[laughs]
[Mary] Oh my gosh!
-Holy shit!
-[Jason] This is a little aggressive.
[Maya] Fuck. Can you turn down the snow?
I love you.
[Heather] Oh God.
[Davina] Too much. Too much.
[Maya] My God, cover me.
[Mary] No, this is dry clean only.
[laughter]
[Amanza] It's really cold.
Hi.
Oh my God.
-The snow is beautiful!
-[Christian] It's really cool.
[man] We are gathered here today,
to celebrate
one of life's greatest moments.
Today, Christine and Christian
celebrate their romance together
with a new life
that they undertake together.
Now marriage requires love.
A word we often use
with vagueness and sentimentality,
when in fact
it is our natural state of being.
These are the rings that you,
Christine, and you, Christian,
will wear for the rest of your lives.
Rings are circles,
symbols that remind us of that
which has no beginning and no end.
[emotional pop playing]
♪ I can swear I saw in your eyes
What you saw in mine ♪
♪ Though I deny it's the first try ♪
♪ I can swear I saw in your heart
What you saw in mine ♪
♪ Blind faith
To be swept away a long, long time ♪
And let us grant that the love
which you both have for each other now
may always be so.
♪ It's our dream ♪
♪ Calling for me, calling for me
Calling for me out of sight ♪
♪ Think I'd just rather be ♪
♪ Drownin' in the, drownin' in the
Drownin' in the perfect lie ♪
[cheering, applause]
[guests whooping]
[Heather] Oh. Cheers.
-What'd you think? Beautiful, right?
-[Maya] It was really beautiful.
So dramatic.
It was a winter wonderland.
-[Maya] Chrishell is there.
-You think she's okay?
-'Cause she start--
-[Maya] I don't think she's okay.
[Heather, Maya] She seems really sad.
[Jason] Thank you for not objecting.
-[Chrishell] What?
-For not objecting. To the wedding.
[Chrishell] I didn't even catch that part.
I missed my cue.
I know. I was like, "Wait a minute."
-That would be funny.
-You're like,
"But wait,
I haven't even had a chance to…"
-You wanna sit here?
-[Jason] I guess I'll sit.
[groans]
-[Heather] Are these hot chocolates?
-[Jason] Go ahead, I've had one.
-[Heather] What is that?
-You wanna split one?
[Heather] Oh, I can't, honey. I'm vegan.
[laughs]
-Look at his eye roll.
-He rolled his eyes at me.
[Jason] Wow, that was--
I didn't go to your wedding but--
that was probably--
that's the most beautiful venue
I've seen in a wedding.
-That was well done. Well thought out.
-Well…
Chrishell's like,
"Can we not talk about mine?"
[scoffs] It's pointless
if you had gone to it.
[indistinct chatter]
-[Brett] Hey, that's the girl I talked to.
-[Davina] How's that going? Well?
-Oh, yeah. It's a done deal.
-She wants a piece?
-[Heather] Who is she?
-She made the dress.
-She made the dress?
-Yeah.
She's one of the seamstresses.
-I'm gonna go say hi real quick.
-Look at him. Working it.
[Heather] There's no way
he'll hook up with her.
-[Davina] I don't think so either.
-[Heather laughs]
[Amanza] How's your place looking
since I--
-'cause I haven't seen it since you got--
-It's good.
It's really coming together, and now
I feel like it's really light and bright,
and I feel like
it reflects my personality a little more.
[Maya] You're getting comfortable?
-Yeah.
You've done so much. I mean, the fact
that you've moved in, you've redecorated,
and then pulled it together
to come tonight…
It was maybe just a little tough,
but honestly,
-I'm glad I came and--
-We're glad you came.
You're a strong girl.
Yeah.
So Heather, I saw your article
-that you did about Chrishell.
-But…
Did you show it to her?
No. I found it.
It wasn't about Chrishell though.
Tarek and I were doing an interview
about us moving in together.
And the reporter just, like…
asking us about
me and Tarek's, like, life,
and how we're adjusting,
and then slipped in,
"Oh, and how are you
supporting Chrishell?" And then--
[Davina] Everything you said
was super supportive.
So all they did was ask
how you supported her?
Yes. It wasn't like
they interviewed me about Chrishell.
It was an interview about Tarek and I.
Then two hours later, there you go.
It came out that soon? Two hours later?
It is a vulnerable situation to be in.
They are asking anyone
that has ever known me ever,
for any kind of a comment.
And I'll see these comments
that aren't true…
-Yeah.
-…and it's hard…
because I'm also being told legally
don't say anything. So--
You can't even defend it.
You just have to sit there
and let these lies being spread.
[Chrishell] At this moment, there are
so many things that I'd like to say,
but none of them
are gonna be good right now.
I'm just trying to keep my mouth shut.
Because I was married to someone
that's a public figure,
I have to be extremely careful
what I say legally,
and this is certainly not
a safe environment.
And also,
this is someone's wedding, you know?
The last thing I wanna do
is cause a scene at someone's wedding.
But I am sorry.
Of course. I totally understand it.
I should know better.
No, it's okay.
You're the only one
that has any right to say anything.
We gotta support her.
Keep our mouths shut.
The rest of us are just like,
"No comment.
We support her, she's the best."
I'm not backing anybody up here,
but I'm just saying
everyone has their own side
in every situation, right?
When you didn't invite me to your wedding,
that was your choice.
I had my side of the story,
and you had your side, is that right?
That's right.
No. She's our family.
She is our friend, and so it's her side.
-Always.
-We don't know any details.
[Mary] If you even said there's always
two sides to the story to the press,
thinking, "We love her, we support her,
but there's two sides to the story,"
-do you know what that can do to her?
-We don't know any details.
That's fucked up.
There's a respectful side
and a non-respectful side--
a way to handle things.
But literally, I know zero.
Like, I know nothing.
You know what I mean?
So what do you want me to say?
There's not two sides.
-There are.
-He's wrong, she's right,
and we support her. That's it!
[Davina] But Chrishell, to be fair,
obviously, Justin has his own side, right?
Can we stop?
That's all I'm saying.
You didn't get married
to get divorced, you know?
You know that, right?
-That's all I wanna say.
-I don't wanna do this anymore.
[Davina repeats] She's gonna leave.
No, let her go.
Right? Amanza, should we let her go?
I'm gonna fucking kill her. Chrishell?
What do you think, Amanza?
Did we offend her?
I can tell you what she's feeling.
She's, like,
"I'm at the fucking wedding,
talking about it is just too much."
It's like, "I'm holding it together
the best that I can.
Please stop!"
Amanza, we wanna be there for her,
but I don't know
if she wants us to be there.
You know what I mean?
That's how I feel.
[Brett] You are insanely fit, by the way.
-Do you work out or…
-[woman] Yes, and you? You like the gym?
[Brett] What the fuck--
Hold on one second.
Are you alright?
She's out, dude. She's over it.
She's fucking outta here.
Who the fuck upset Chrishell?
[Heather] I wanna enjoy the wedding.
[Amanza] Mary's pissed.
Maybe Mary shouldn't have brought it up.
Oy.
["Castle" playing]
♪ High up in my castle ♪
♪ Dancing with the devil ♪
♪ Trippin' on you ♪
♪ Push it 'til we break it ♪
♪ See how far we take it ♪
♪ When I'm with you ♪
[Romain] What happened earlier?
-With what?
-Chrishell and, like, this whole thing?
She stormed out because they were saying
there's always two sides to the story
when it…
-Who said there is two sides of the story?
-Davina was getting heated a little bit--
That girl. She's, like, a fucking snake.
-I know.
-Goodness.
There are two sides to the story.
I'm not defending the guy
-but we don't know.
-I wouldn't say that.
-I'd say you can't tell from the outside.
-[Davina] Yeah, you can't tell.
I don't think there's any excuse
to blindside your wife.
[Davina] That's what we're saying.
But "there's two sides to a story"
is a weird way to say
you can never judge a relationship
from the outside.
She's always, always,
every time there's an argument,
every single time…
the snake show up.
[Chrishell] Getting confronted
by my co-workers is frustrating.
But… you know what?
Maybe Davina is right.
You know,
there are two sides to every story,
and maybe it's time
that I start writing a new one.
[dramatic pop playing]
Yes!
You're next, babe!
♪ Time, oh, it is time ♪
♪ To rectify ♪
♪ So I raise my fists
And swallow down my pride ♪
♪ Well I raise my flag
And I will lead the fight ♪